rapidfileshare.net 2015-06-07

# RapidFileShare - EgyszerЕ± mГіdja, hogy megosszd az ГЎllomГЎnyaidat

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you many be asked to enter your name and email address. You may however visit our site anonymously as well. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- To offer a weekly email to our users which includes discounts and only ever comes from us. You may opt-out of this as well.

\- To personalize your experience with your name and email we are able to better respond to your needs

\- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from our customers)

\- To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your service requests and support needs)

\- To process transactions; your information whether public or private will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or given to any other company for any reason whatsover without your consent.

\- To send periodic emails for new services and exciting news from us.

\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, and related service information.

Note: If at anytime you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we can be contacted at anytime from our contact us page to notify us of this requirement. There is also a link to unsubscribe from our emails in all emails sent out.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the highest levels of security and safety of your personal information. As mentioned, we will in no way share any information about any one of our customers without notification or consent.

**Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties anything about any site member.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion we may include or offer third pary products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. The only reason we will offer third party links is if we feel it may enhance the user experience from our site by offering our users complimentary services. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. Any changes made to this policy will be made on this page, thus making this page the most recent version of our privacy policy.
